<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Wanru Zhao 赵婉如</title>
    <link>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="Ryan0v0.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>/Ryan0v0.github.io/images/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual Tutoring System for Piano Training based on AR&#43;AI</title>
      <link>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/ar-piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/ar-piano/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presented an AR-based piano performance training system, which supports better user experience with significantly less cognitive load and increases learning efficiency and quality compared to traditional teaching patterns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implemented Viterbi Algorithm in machine learning through pre-trained Hidden Markov Model to determine  appropriate fingerings for specific notes and note sequences.
Generated 3D animation of hand motion automatically based on the determined fingerings. These virtual hand demonstrations are rendered in head-mounted displays and registered with a real piano to provide users with real-time visual guidance and feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submitted a paper to IEEE VR 2021 and it is under review.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducted user study and promoted product practical application as a startup company product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartCity Visualization System for 3D Traffic Dangerous Pattern Prediction</title>
      <link>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/smartcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>Ryan0v0.github.io/project/smartcity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Took risky patterns as the keystones in danger management, and built causality networks among them for pain points identification, attribution and prediction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used Spark and Hadoop to analyze the large-scale daily data in Beijing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Built a 3D Geographic Information System(GIS) Visualization Platform using WebGL, D3.js and Leaflet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
